http://www.visionsfantastic.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy – Visions Fantastic
Skip to toolbar
About WordPressWordPress.orgDocumentationSupportFeedbackLog InRegisterSearch
Skip to content
Visions Fantastic
The Sights and Sounds of Disneyland
Search for:
Forums
Disneyland Resort DiscussionDisneyland Resort Hotel DiscussionSite Feedback and Help
GroupsActivity
The Disneyland Resort
Disneyland Park
Main Street USAAdventurelandFrontierlandNew Orleans SquareCritter CountryGalaxy’s EdgeFantasylandMickey’s ToontownTomorrowland
Disney California Adventure
Buena Vista StreetAvengers CampusCars LandGrizzly PeakHollywood LandPacific WharfPixar Pier
Downtown DisneyDisney’s Grand Californian HotelThe Disneyland HotelParadise Pier HotelDisneyland Resort ShoppingDisneyland Resort DiningDisneyland Resort Entertainment
Visions Fantastic RadioEventsDaddyB’s Disneyland on your DesktopPrivacy PolicyContact Us
Privacy Policy
Social Share
Who we are
Our website address is: http://www.visionsfantastic.com.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact formsOur site may use a Contact Form and ask for your email address. Your IP address may be logged with form submission.
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
AnalyticsWe occasionally use information such as your IP address to gauge repeat visits.
Who we share your data withNo One
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Your contact informationVisions Fantastic650 E. Harvard AvenueFresno, CA 93704559-970-6964
Additional informationUsers are able to self-delete their accounts from their User Control Panel.
Tweet
Login with your Social Account
Current song: Loading ...
Stream title:
Bit rate:
Current listeners:
Maximum listeners:
Server status:
AutoDJ status:
Source connected:
Station time:
Current playlist:
Track details:
-
-
Raw metadata:
Loading ...
VisionsFantastic.com All images (C) VisionsFantastic.com and Brett “DaddyB” Garrett and may not be used, duplicated or altered for other uses.
Spam blocked17 340 spam blocked by CleanTalk
Copyright © 2020 Visions Fantastic. All Rights Reserved. Privacy PolicyCatch Mag by Catch Themes
Scroll Up
Home>Privacy Policy
Scroll UpScroll Up
